<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>nevstokes.com</title>
    <link>https://nevstokes.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on nevstokes.com</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 20:13:38 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://nevstokes.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting Afresh</title>
      <link>https://nevstokes.com/blog/starting-afresh/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2020 20:13:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nevstokes.com/blog/starting-afresh/</guid>
      <description>At some point, thanks to various harddrive failures and misplaced USB sticks, I lost the backups of my old Wordpress site. Let&amp;rsquo;s face it, its demise is certainly no great loss for humanity. After a long break, what better time than lockdown to restart the cathartic outpourings?
Hopefully my writing will be a tad more focussed that my previous inane ramblings - although there&amp;rsquo;s little doubt that those will remain. I plan on writing more about my work; development and engineering, touching on various languages, containers, cloud architectures, tools and practices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>https://nevstokes.com/page/about-me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nevstokes.com/page/about-me/</guid>
      <description>Not only a fantastic Jackie Chan movie, but a perfectly valid question. You&amp;rsquo;re reading this so I&amp;rsquo;m assuming you have at least a passing curiosity as to my background.
There&amp;rsquo;s likely much more to be gleaned from following the social links way down there in the footer but, by way of brevity (not my strong point), here&amp;rsquo;s the précis:
Although I was born and raised in Halifax, West Yorkshire, I&amp;rsquo;ve lived in Edinburgh, Scotland for pretty much all of my adult life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colophon</title>
      <link>https://nevstokes.com/page/colophon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://nevstokes.com/page/colophon/</guid>
      <description>The site is published with Hugo, hosted on GitHub Pages, and with SSL and CDN provided by Cloudflare.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>