<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Pages on nevstokes.com</title><link>https://nevstokes.com/page/</link><description>Recent content in Pages on nevstokes.com</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><atom:link href="https://nevstokes.com/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About Me</title><link>https://nevstokes.com/page/about-me/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nevstokes.com/page/about-me/</guid><description>Not only a fantastic Jackie Chan movie, but a perfectly valid question, given the circumstances. You&amp;rsquo;re reading this so I&amp;rsquo;m assuming you have at least a passing curiosity as to my background.
There&amp;rsquo;s likely much more to be gleaned from following the social links way down there in the footer but, by way of brevity (not my strong point), here&amp;rsquo;s the précis:
Although I was born and raised in Halifax, West Yorkshire, I&amp;rsquo;ve lived in Edinburgh, Scotland for pretty much all of my adult life.</description></item><item><title>Accessibility Statement</title><link>https://nevstokes.com/page/accessibility/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nevstokes.com/page/accessibility/</guid><description>From working in design agencies where accessibility was just good practice, to local government where it was mandatory, I&amp;rsquo;ve always felt that inclusive design was the right thing to do. I also feel that it&amp;rsquo;s important that this page is given an equal navigational standing and isn&amp;rsquo;t burried somewhere in among the footnotes.
It is my aim that the website is usable regardless of browser, device, connection speed, or physical ability.</description></item><item><title>Colophon</title><link>https://nevstokes.com/page/colophon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://nevstokes.com/page/colophon/</guid><description>The site is published by the Hugo static site generator, hosted on GitHub Pages. The domain, security certificate and content delivery network is provided by Cloudflare. Availability is monitored by UptimeRobot.
Social icons were selected from the Simple Brand library and the theme icons chosen from Feather, used under the CC0 1.0 Universal License and MIT respectively. SVGs for both were generated by IcoMoon.
Fonts in use are Quicksand for general content in conjunction with Source Code Pro for monospaced text, both used under the Open Font License.</description></item></channel></rss>